- [Instructor] This class is for an intermediate
to advanced level.
And in order to get the most out of this course,
you should know about the basics
of web development, such as HTML to create webpages,
and you should also understand
how to change the appearance of a webpage
by using the CSS rules.
And some knowledge of JavaScript and ES6
will be useful as well.
A basic understanding
of React development is highly recommended,
meaning that you should know
how to create a React component,
how to pass data down to child components
by using the props, how to create interactions,
and also understand how to use the hooks,
which have been available since the version 16.8 of React,
in order to create functional and stateful components.
It will also be helpful to have some experience
and to know one package manager like npm
in order to run scripts.
So what you should know
is how to change directory by running cd,
and also display the list of files and folders
included in a directory with ls.
And finally, you can run npm start
in order to start a project created with Create React app.
So if you have answered yes to every technical requirements,
this is perfect.
You are all set and ready to enjoy the class.